<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[The Secret of Everything]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[The Secret of Everything]]></description>
        <link>http://thesecretofeverything.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 20:04:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://thesecretofeverything.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Secret of Everything]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/054c21a7-ab28-4dc2-8799-76c0683e0da1.jpg">,<h1>The Secret of Everything</h1>,<h2>Don’t Just “Get It” – Experience It – NOW!</h2>,<p>For a long time after I first learned about the 3 Principles – the so called ‘inside-out’ understanding – I noticed I often felt I was “getting it” intellectually – but that something was still missing. It seemed like I wasn’t really getting it all at an experiential level.</p>,<p>And it seemed this was something many other people were struggling with.</p>,<p>It took me just around 2 years to finally see through – and past – what turned out to have been just an innocent misunderstanding. And what then became very clear to me was – that it really is possible for all of us to experience “The Secret of Everything” – not tomorrow – or sometime in the future – but right now!</p>,<p>So – if you’ve ever noticed yourself saying – or thinking to yourself – something along the lines of … “I understand this intellectually – but that doesn’t seem to be enough. I just don’t seem to ‘get it’ experientially” – and you’d like to see, hear and experience something “deeper” – I’m running The Secret of Everything – Don’t Just “Get It” – Experience It – Now – online program – especially for you (and for me because it’s fun!).</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://thesecretofeverything.com/the-secret-of-everything/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a12a9d9c-2dc8-414b-8ddb-d69629322df0</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 14:22:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>